<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog|Abhishek</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:07 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:07 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.7</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spending a Year at IIT Bombay</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Weeks went by and I started hearing the word ‘acads’ more often. It was the “Mid Sem” time. It was the first exam which carried a good amount of weightage in the academic performance and I was not a “maggu” after all. After looking at the tutorials, the first instinct I got was that I should at least manage to pass. But as time passed and I managed balance between acads and timepass, I started getting better expectations from myself. And now here I was, at the brink of answering the mid sem.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The lecture halls and canteens remained open...</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 17:56:40 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>/spending-a-year-at-iit-bombay/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/spending-a-year-at-iit-bombay/</guid>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>life</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spending a Year at IIT Bombay</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;IIT Bombay, one of the most prestigious institutes in India and the world offers a little more, actually a lot more than just education. Having spent a year at this premiere institute where you will find crème de la crème, I have some things to express.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/iitb/IMG_20190726_120753.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;29 June 2019: It was 6 in the morning when I landed in Mumbai with my parents. As we were heading towards my dream college, several thoughts popped up in my mind. How I learnt about IITs ? How has the struggle been for the last 2 years ? What...</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 17:56:40 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>/spending-a-year-at-iit-bombay/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/spending-a-year-at-iit-bombay/</guid>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>life</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Abhishek Pai Angle</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2001 06:27:01 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>/teste/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/teste/</guid>
        
        <category></category>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
